<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>novprog.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">NovProg</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">NovProg</name>
  <summary>Wordcount graphing program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein grafisches Programm zum Wörter zählen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Πρόγραμμα γραφικής απεικόνισης καταμέτρησης κειμένου</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Programme de suivi statistique de comptage de mots</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Žodžių apskaitos vaizdavimo programa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een programma voor het in kaart brengen van het aantal woorden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Program graficzny podsumowania liczby słów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Programa gráfico de contagem de palavras</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Program contorizare grafică a cuvintelor</summary>

  <description>
    <p>NovProg is a tool to graph your progress in writing a novel. You enter your wordcount and it updates a graph showing you how much progress you have made. It also shows you how far you are through your daily goal, and your total goal. Mousing over a bar in the graph will show a tooltip with that day’s wordcount.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">NovProg ist ein Werkzeug, dass grafisch Ihren Fortschritt einen Roman zu schreiben darstellt. Sie geben Ihre Wortanzahl ein und eine Grafik zeigt Ihnen, wie weit Sie gekommen sind. Es zeigt Ihnen auch, wie weit Sie von Ihren täglichen und Ihren insgesamten Ziel entfernt sind. Beim Bewegen der Maus über einen Balken im Diagramm, wird ein Tooltip mit der Wortanzahl des heutigen Tages angezeigt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το NovProg είναι εργαλείο που προσφέρει γραφική απεικόνιση της προόδου σας στη συγγραφή ενός έργου. Εισάγετε την καταμέτρηση λέξεών σας και αυτό θα ενημερώνει το γράφημα που θα σας δείχνει πόσο μεγάλη πρόοδο έχετε κάνει. Επίσης σας δείχνει πόσο μακριά είστε από τον ημερήσιο και τον συνολικό σας στόχο. Μετακινώντας το δείκτη του ποντικιού πάνω από μια γραμμή στο διάγραμμα, θα εμφανιστεί μια επεξήγηση εργαλείου με την καταμέτρηση λέξεων εκείνης της ημέρας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">NovProg est un outil permettant d'afficher le graphique de progression de l'écriture de votre roman. Vous n'avez qu'à entrer votre nombre de mots et il met à jour un graphique vous affichant les progrès effectués. Il vous montre également la distance à votre objectif quotidien et votre objectif total. En survolant à la souris une barre du graphe, vous verrez une annotation avec le nombre de mots rédigés ce jour là.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">NovProg yra įrankis, kuris vaizduoja jūsų novelės rašymo eigą. Jūs įvedate žodžių apskaitą ir programa atnaujina grafiką, rodantį kiek pažengėte. Programa taip pat rodo, kiek įveikėte savo kasdienio tikslo ir galutinio tikslo. Užvedę pėle ant stulpelių, pamatysite tam tikros dienos žodžių apskaitą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">NovProg helpt u bij het schrijven van een verhaal door de schrijfvoortgang in kaart te brengen. Voer het aantal woorden in om een grafiek op te maken die de voortgang toont. Ook toont het programma of u al dichter bij uw dagelijkse en totale doel bent gekomen. Als u de muis op een balk houdt, zal er een ballon verschijnen die het aantal woorden van die dag toont.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">NovProg jest narzędziem do wykresu twojego postępu w pisaniu powieści. Wprowadzasz twoją liczbę słów i aktualizujesz wykres, pokazujący twój aktualny postęp. Program pokazuje również, jak daleko jesteś oddalony od twojego codziennego i całkowitego celu. Najeżdżając myszką na słupek w wykresie, pojawi się tooltip z dzisiejszą liczbą słów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O NovProg é uma ferramenta para criar gráficos do progresso de uma novela escrita. Introduz-se a contagem de palavras e o programa atualiza um gráfico que mostra o progresso que fez. Também mostra quão longe está do objetivo diário e do objetivo total. Ao passar com o cursor sobre uma barra do gráfico é mostrada a informação com a contagem de palavras do dia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">NovProg este un instrument de reprezentare grafică a progresului în scrierea unui roman. Introduceţi nr. de cuvinte şi se actualizează un grafic care vă arată cît de mult aţi progresat. De asemenea, vă arată cît de departe sînteţi de obiectivul dvs. de zi cu zi, şi obiectivul dvs. total. Mişcînd mouse-ul pe o bară din grafic vă va arăta o bulă de informaţii cu nr. de cuvinte din acea zi.</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gottcode.org/novprog/screenshots/appdata.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://gottcode.org/novprog/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gottcode.org/novprog/bugs/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://gottcode.org/tip/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/gottcode/novprog/</url>

  <developer id="org.gottcode">
    <name translatable="no">Graeme Gott</name>
  </developer>
  <update_contact>graeme@gottcode.org</update_contact>

  <translation type="qt">novprog</translation>

  <provides>
    <binary>novprog</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">novprog.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="stock">novprog</icon>

  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>Chart</category>
  </categories>

  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>

  <releases>
    <release version="3.2.3" date="2024-01-16">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Turkish</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.2.2" date="2023-01-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.2.1" date="2022-05-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Switched to Qt 6</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.2.0" date="2021-09-21">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added setting words written for current day</li>
          <li>Added support for Qt 6</li>
          <li>Refactored code</li>
          <li>Removed XPM icon</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Dutch, Lithuanian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.7" date="2020-04-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Did not load locales with underscores</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.6" date="2019-08-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Window icon didn't work in Wayland</li>
          <li>Improved loading locales</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.5" date="2018-07-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Automatic high DPI support</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.4" date="2018-05-29">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Extra warnings only shown in debug build</li>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Improved macOS deployment</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Portuguese</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
